(Leonard:)When did we get
a wall safe?
(Sheldon:)When there was no more room
in the floor safe.
(Leonard:)When did we get
a floor safe?
(Sheldon:)When we got the security camera.
(Leonard:)There's a
security camera?
(Sheldon:)Aquaman, protecting your home
since 2012.
(Penny:)Oh, my God.
We've done things on that couch.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. You don't have to tell me.
(Raj:)So, your father-in-law
is in there right now?
(Howard:)Yes. So back me up.
(Howard:)The house is good the way it is.
Oh, okay. Got it.
(Howard:)Hey. What's going on?
(Sheldon:)Hey.
Hey, Raj.
(Bernadette:)Dad and I were just talking
about taking down this wall.
(Raj:)You sure? It's a...
pretty great wall.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)What's so great about it?
(Raj:)I'm sorry.
I did what I could.
(Bernadette:)Seriously? You brought Raj over
to take your side?
(Howard:)Your dad's on your side.
(Bernadette:)He's not on my side. He's doing
all the work for free.